<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="agreement_title" translatable="false" >《JGW Wallet User Service Agreement》 </string>
    <string name="agreement_content" translatable="false" >


Version1.0 2018-06-11  \n\t

The “JGW Wallet User Service Agreement” (hereinafter referred to as “This Agreement”) is entered into by and between JGW and user (hereinafter referred to as “You” or “User”), this agreement shall have contractual legal effect between you and JGW. \n\t

Before you use the service provided by us, please carefully read this agreement, especially the clause of “Exemption and Limitation of Liabilities” stipulated in this agreement, which shall be reflected in bold form, so as to ensure you to fully understand the terms under this agreement, and to independently consider related risks. \n\t

1.	Regarding the Recognition and Acceptance of This Agreement \n\t

1.1 You understand that this agreement and related agreements shall be applicable to JGW Wallet as well as the applications and services independently developed and owned by JGW on JGW Wallet, including but not limited to the decentralization application (or “DApp”) (excluding DApp developed by any third party), centralization application (or “App”) (excluding DApp developed by any third party). \n\t

1.2 You downloading of JGW Wallet software and establishment or input of wallet shall be deemed that you have fully read and accepted all terms under this agreement, this agreement shall immediately come into effect, and have binding force on both parties. \n\t

1.3 This agreement can be updated by JGW at any time, once the modified agreement is issued, it shall immediately and automatically come into effect without separate notification. After JGW releases terms of the modification agreement, if you don’t accept the terms after modification, please immediately stop using JGW Wallet, your continuous use of JGW Wallet shall be deemed as your acceptance of the modified agreement. \n\t

1.4 Before using our service, please confirm that you have turned 18 years old. \n\t

2.	Definition of Nouns \n\t

2.1  “JGW Wallet” means the mobile app client-side of the software platform website that JGW develops, operates, manages and has legal ownership of, it provides local wallet of block chain assets, escrow account and other related services, it has the domain name of www. JGW Wallet.com, support using on Android system and iOS system. JGW uses this software to provide users with local and online management service of block chain digital assets. \n\t

2.2 User: \n\t

 (1) A user must be a natural person with full capacity for civil conduct; \n\t

 (2) If you are minor below 18 years old and uses JGW Wallet service, you need to use JGW Wallet under the instruction by your parents or guardian. If a person without capacity of civil conduct uses JGW Wallet or a person with limited capacity for civil conduct engages in any transaction beyond his/her civil rights or capacity, for any and all consequences caused hereof, JGW Wallet shall have the right to require you and your guardian to take responsibility. \n\t

2.3 “Block Chain” means a type of linked data structure generated by connecting data blocks in sequence, and it uses the method of cryptology to guarantee its distributed ledger that can’t be altered nor forged. It uses linked data structure to verify and store data, uses distributed nodes and consensus algorithm to generate and update data, uses the method of cryptology to guarantee the safety of data transmission and access, and uses smart contract composed of automated script code to program and operate data, it is a brand-new type of distributed infrastructure and computing paradigm. \n\t

2.4 “Block Chain Asset or Digital Asset” means the digits stored in the cryptology account in block chain data, it is deemed as the digital asset of the legal owner of account, including but not limited to Bitcoin, Ethereum, etc. \n\t

2.5 “Wallet Password” means the password that the software operating interface asks you to fill in the process when you establish JGW Wallet, such password is used for encipherment protection of private key. As a decentralized application, wallet password is not stored in this mobile device of yours nor the server of JGW, once you lost it, you will need to use cleartext private key or mnemonic word to reset new password. \n\t

2.6 “Mnemonic Word” meets the block chain BIP39 industrial standard, and is composed of 12 orderly words generated from random algorithm. It is the easy-to-record form of private key, and convenient for users to keep as backup. The process of establishing mnemonic word is a local behavior of client-side, and can be operated without network connection, and it has nothing to do with the service side, so JGW Wallet doesn’t have user’s mnemonic word, can’t manage wallet assets for user, and can’t recover mnemonic word for user. JGW Wallet follows BIP32, BIP39 and BIP44 standards, any other wallet following such standards may use the same mnemonic word to recover and manage your block chain assets. \n\t

2.7 “Miner Fee” means the transaction confirmation expense paid to block chain miner node when users transfer assets on block chain, such fee is charged by the miner. \n\t

2.8 “Personal Information” means the various information that is recorded in electronic or other means and can be used to identify user’s personal identity individually or by integrating with other information, including but not limited to natural person’s name, birth date, ID certificate number, personal biometric identification information, residence, telephone number, bank card number, mail address, wallet address, mobile device information, operating record, transaction record, etc., but excluding user’s wallet password, private key, mnemonic word. \n\t

3.	Service Content \n\t

3.1 “Establishment or Input of Wallet”: for digital assets supported by JGW Wallet, you may use JGW Wallet to generate new wallet or use mnemonic word to input the previously generated wallet. \n\t

3.2 \n\t “Transfer, Collection”: you may use the transfer or collection function of JGW Wallet to implement management of digital assets, meaning using private key for electronic signature, modifying ledger of related block chain. Transfer means that the payer uses the payee’s block chain address to implement transfer operation, both the actual transfer and collection behaviors occur in related block chain system (rather than JGW Wallet). \n\t

3.3 “Transaction Record”: we will use block chain system to copy the entire or partial transaction records of yours. The transaction record shall be in accordance with the record in corresponding block chain system. \n\t

3.4 “Management of Digital Assets”. You may use JGW Wallet to add, keep or remove the digital assets supported by JGW Wallet. \n\t

3.5 \n\t “Browsing DApp”: through the link on JGW Wallet, users may skip to DApp and use services provided by such DApp (including JGW’s own DApp and third-party DApp). Browsing DApp. through the link on JGW Wallet, users may skip to DApp and use services provided by such DApp (including JGW’s own DApp and third-party DApp). \n\t

3.6 “Suspension or Cancellation”. You know that based on the “Irrevocability” property of the block-chain-system-based transaction, we can’t suspend or cancel coin issuing or other operations for you. \n\t

3.7 Other services that JWG believes necessary to provide. \n\t

4.	Privacy Clause \n\t

JGW attaches importance to protection of user privacy, for related privacy protection policies, please refer to the “JGW Wallet Privacy Policy” released and updated by JGW from time to time. \n\t

5.	Risk Warning \n\t

5.1 You understand and know that the laws and regulations in the field of digital assets are not complete yet, digital assets in such field may generate major risks of failure in realization, unstable technology, loss, etc. Besides, the price fluctuation degree of digital assets is far higher than that of other financial assets. We prudently remind you that you should rationally choose to hold or dispose any type of digital assets based on your own financial status and risk preference. \n\t

5.2 When using JGW Wallet services, if you or your counterparty fails to comply with the operating notes or rules in this agreement or related website notes or transaction and payment pages, JGW Wallet shall not guarantee smooth completion of such transaction, and JGW Wallet shall not bear liability of damage compensation. In case of the circumstance above, and such payment has been transferred to the JGW Wallet or third-party wallet of you or your trading partner, you understand the “Irrevocability” property of the block chain operation, and the “Irrevocability” feature of related transaction, you and your counterparty shall bear corresponding risks and consequences on your own. \n\t

5.3 When you use any third-party DApp integrated by JGW Wallet for service or having transaction, for your own interest, JGW suggests you to carefully read this agreement and JGW Wallet notes, understand trading counterparty and product information, discretely evaluate risks before taking action. Any and all transaction behaviors by you at third-party DApp shall be your own behaviors, the contractual relationship with binding force is established between you and your counterparty, and shall have nothing to do with JGW Wallet. JGW Wallet shall not bear any liability for any and all risks, liabilities, losses and expenses incurred from your transaction behaviors. \n\t

5.4 You shall independently judge in transaction process on whether the counterparty is a person with full capacity for civil conduct or not and independently decide whether to transact with or transfer to the counterparty or not, and you shall bear all the related risks hereof. 

5.5 In the process of transfer, if there is “Failed Transaction”, “Packaging Overtime” or other similar abnormal information cues, you shall reconfirm it through the official channel of related block chain system or other block chain inquiry tool, so as to avoid repeated transfer; otherwise, any and all losses and expenses incurred hereof shall be at your own cost. \n\t

5.6 You understand that after you establish or input wallet on JGW Wallet, your private key, mnemonic word and other information shall only be stored in current mobile device, and shall not be stored on JGW Wallet or JGW’s server. You may replace mobile device by adopting wallet synchronization according to the operating guides provided by JGW Wallet. But if you fail to store or backup wallet password, private key, mnemonic word or other related information and you have lost your mobile device, your digital assets will be lost and JGW will be unable to recover it for you, you will need to bear corresponding losses on your own. If you have any leakage when exporting, storing or backup of wallet password, private key, mnemonic word or other related information, or the device or service storing or backing up the foresaid information is attacked or controlled by a hacker, your digital assets will be lost for this reason, and JGW will be unable to recover it for you, and you shall bear corresponding losses on your own. \n\t

5.7 We suggest you to make safe backup of your wallet password, private key, mnemonic word or other related information when you establish or input wallet. We remind you to take a note, please don’t adopt the following backup methods: screenshot, email, notepad, short message, WeChat, QQ and other electronic backup. We suggest you to write down mnemonic word and other information on notebook in paper, meanwhile, you may also keep electronic data to password manager. \n\t

5.8 We suggest you to use JGW Wallet in safe network environment, so as to prevent your mobile device from jailbreak or Root, and prevent possible potential safety hazards. \n\t

5.9 In the process of using our services, please be alert about fraudulent behaviors that are not from JGW Wallet official. Once finding such behaviors, we encourage you to inform us immediately. \n\t

6.	Change, Terminal and Termination of Service \n\t

6.1 You agree that JGW may temporarily provide partial service functions or suspend partial service functions or open new service functions in the future in order to guarantee independent operating right. For any decrease or increase or change of any function, as long as you still use the services provided by JGW, it means that you still agree to this agreement or the terms after modification of this agreement. \n\t

6.2 You understand that JGW will suspend provision of services in case of the following circumstances: \n\t

 (1) Business is interrupted due to maintenance, upgrading, fault or communication disruption of devices or block chain system or due to other technical reasons; \n\t

 (2) JWG system is unable to provide services or JGW reasonably believes that there will be relatively high risk in continuously providing service due to typhoon, earthquake, flood, outage, war, terrorist attack or other force majeure factors, virus, trojan, hacker attack, system instability or government action or other related reasons; \n\t

 (3) Occurrence of other circumstances there JGW couldn’t control or reasonably predict. \n\t

6.3 When you have any of the following circumstances, JGW may unilaterally suspend or terminate partial or entire functions of JGW Wallet that you are using \n\t

 (1) Death of user; \n\t

 (2) Theft of other people’s wallet information or mobile device; \n\t

 (3) The personal information provided by you is unauthentic; \n\t

 (4) Reject any forced updating operation initiated by JGW for enhancing JGW Wallet functions; \n\t

 (5) Use JGW Wallet for any illegal or criminal activity; \n\t

 (6) Obstruct normal use by other users; \n\t

 (7) Pretend to be staff or management personnel of JGW; \n\t

 (8) Attack, intrude into, change or threat the normal operation of JGW computer system in any other way; \n\t

 (9) Use JGW Wallet to distribute spam; \n\t

 (10) Spread rumors, damage the goodwill of JGW and JGW Wallet; \n\t

 (11) Breach of law, other behaviors in violation of this agreement, and the circumstances where JGW reasonably believes that the function should be suspended. \n\t

6.4 When the service relation between you and JGW is changed, suspended or terminated, you still have the right to export your wallet and other related information within reasonable time. \n\t

7.	Your Commitment to Legally Use JGW Services \n\t

7.1 You shall comply with the laws and regulations of the country or region where you live, shall not use JGW Wallet for any illegal purpose, and shall not use JGW services in any illegal way. \n\t

7.2 You shall not use JGW Wallet to engage in any illegal or criminal behaviors, including but not limited to: \n\t

 (1) Jeopardize national security, leak national secrets, subvert state political power, undermine national unity; \n\t

 (2) Engage in any illegal or criminal behavior, including but not limited to money laundering, illegal fundraising, etc.; \n\t

 (3) Access to JGW service, collect or process the contents provided by JGW, intervene or try to intervene any user by using any automated programing, software, engine, web crawler, website analytical tool, data mining tool or similar tools, or behavior of accessing to JGW services in any other method; \n\t

 (4) Provide gambling information or induce others to participate in gambling in any other method; \n\t

 (5) Intrude into other people’s JGW Wallet to steel digital assets; \n\t

 (6) Have any transaction with content inconsistent with the transaction content claimed by the counterparty, or have any unauthentic transaction; \n\t

 (7) Engage in any behavior that harms or may harm JGW Wallet service system or data; \n\t

 (8) Other illegal behavior or any behavior that JGW has justifiable reason to consider it as inappropriate. \n\t

7.3 You understand and agree that if you breaks any related law (including but not limited to the regulatory rules of the Customs or Taxation) or any provision of this agreement, which causes JGW to suffer any loss or be subject to any third-party claim or punishment by any administrative agency, you shall compensate JGW, including all reasonable expenses including the lawyer fee paid for claiming rights. \n\t

7.4 You commit to timely pay service fee (if any) to JGW, otherwise JGW shall have the right to suspend or terminate the service provided to you. \n\t

8.	Exception and Limitation of Liability \n\t

8.1 JGW shall only bear liabilities for the obligations clearly listed in this agreement. \n\t

8.2 You understand and agree that JGW may only provide services based on current technical level and conditions within the scope allowed by law. If JGW Wallet is unable to normally provide service for the following reasons, JGW shall not bear liabilities: \n\t

 (1) JGW Wallet system down for maintenance or upgrading; \n\t

 (2) Due to typhoon, earthquake, flood, lightening, terrorist attack or other force majeure causes; \n\t

3) Any fault of your mobile device’s software and hardware, communication wire, power supply wire; \n\t

 (4) Your own mis-operation or using JGW services in the method not authorized or recognized by JGW; \n\t

 (5) Due to virus, trojan, vicious program attack, network jam, system instability, fault of system or equipment, communication fault, electricity fault, causes of bank or governmental action, etc.; \n\t

 (6) Any other reason not due to JGW’s fault. \n\t

8.3 JGW shall not take responsibility for the following circumstances: \n\t

 (1) Loss of digital assets because user loses mobile device, deletes and fails to backup JGW Wallet, deletes and fails to backup wallet, has wallet stolen or forgets wallet password, private key, mnemonic word; \n\t

 (2) Loss of digital assets because user discloses wallet password, private key, mnemonic word on its own, or lends, transfers or authorizes others to use his/her own mobile device or JGW Wallet, or fails to download JGW Wallet application program through the official channel of JGW or uses JGW Wallet application program in other unsafe method; \n\t

 (3) Loss of digital assets due to user’s mis-operation (including but not limited to you inputting transfer address by mistake, problem in the server of transfer node chosen by yourself); \n\t

 (4) Loss of digital assets because of mis-operation caused from user’s failure to understand the nature of block chain technology; \n\t

 (5) Deviation occurred when JGW copies user’s transaction record on block chain due to time lag, instable block chain system and other related reasons; \n\t

 (6) Risks and consequences generated from user’s operation on third-party DApp. \n\t

8.4 You understand that JGW Wallet shall only serve as a tool of your digital assets management. JGW is unable to control the quality, safety or legality of the products and services provided by third-party DApp, the authenticity or accuracy of information, as well as the ability of counterparty to perform the various obligations under the agreement signed with you. All your transaction behaviors made on third-party DApp shall be your own personal behaviors, the contractual relation with binding force shall be established between you and your counterparty, and shall have nothing to do with JGW Wallet. JGW reminds you to judge and determine, at your own discretion, the authenticity, legality and effectiveness of the log-in of DApp and related information. The risks generated from transactions between you and any third party shall also be borne by yourself. \n\t

8.5 JGW may provide services to you and your transaction counterparty at the same time, you agree to clearly exempt JGW from any actual or potential conflict of interest for such possible behavior, and shall not use this to claim any legal defect of JGW when providing services, and shall not aggregate JGW’s liabilities or notice obligations for this reason. \n\t

8.6 JGW shall not provide guarantee in the following forms: \n\t

 (1) JGW’s service will meet all your demands; \n\t

 (2) Any technology, product, service or information that you obtains from JGW will meet your expectation; \n\t

 (3) JGW makes guarantee for the timeliness, accuracy, completeness and reliability of the digital asset market transaction situation and other information grabbed from third-party transactions; \n\t

 (4) Your transaction parties on JGW Wallet will timely perform the various obligations in their transaction agreements reached with you. \n\t

8.7 Under any circumstance, the total amount of liability for compensation for breach of contract that JGW assumes under this agreement shall not exceed 1) 0.1 Ethereum; or 2) RMB 500 (whichever higher). \n\t

8.8 You understand that JGW Wallet shall only serve as a tool for users to manage digital assets and display transaction information, JGW shall not provide legal, taxation or investment suggestions or other related services. You shall seek advises from professionals in the aspects of law, taxation and investment on your own, and for any and all investment loss, data loss, etc. that you suffer in the process of using our service, JGW shall not take any liability. \n\t

8.9 You understand that we may change our user access standard, and the scope and method of providing services to certain group based on requirements of related local policies and regulations. \n\t

9.	Intellectual Property Right Protection \n\t

9.1	 JGW Wallet is an application program that JGW develops and owns intellectual property rights of. The intellectual property rights of any content (including but not limited to this agreement, announcement, article, video, audio, picture, file, information, material, trademark or LOGO) displayed in JGW Wallet shall belong to JGW or third-party right holders. Users may use JGW Wallet application program and its contents only for the purpose of holding and managing digital assets. Without prior written consent from JGW and third-party right holders, nobody may use, modify, decompile, copy, publicly disperse, change, spread, issue or publicly express the foresaid application program and contents without permission. \n\t

10.	Term of Agreement \n\t

10.1 This agreement formed between you and us is a non-fixed-term agreement, if you have any of the following behaviors, we shall have the right to terminate the contract at any time and have it effective right away: \n\t

 (1) You breaks or violates any clause under this agreement; \n\t

 (2) We think that you have abused the application program or service. \n\t

11.	Applicability of Law and Dispute Settlement \n\t

11.1 The effect, interpretation, change, execution and dispute settlement of this agreement and its modified versions shall all be applicable to the laws of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, if there is no related laws, they shall be applicable to international business practices and (or) industrial practices. \n\t

11.2 If there is any dispute or disagreement between you and JGW, it shall be settled firstly through friendly consultation, if such consultation fails, either party may submit it to the local court with jurisdiction where JGW is located. \n\t

12.	Others \n\t

12.1 You need to comprehensively understand and comply with all the related laws, regulations and rules related to your use of JGW services in your judicial jurisdiction. \n\t

12.2 In the process of your use of JGW services, for any problem encountered, you may contact us by submitting feedback on JGW Wallet. \n\t

12.3 You may check this agreement in JGW Wallet. JGW encourages you to check the service agreement of JGW every time when you access to JGW Wallet. \n\t

12.4 This agreement shall be applicable since Jun 22, 2018. \n\t

12.5 Any translation version of this agreement is provided for the convenience of users only, and has no intention of modifying terms of this policy. If there is any conflict between Chinese version of this policy and its non-Chinese version, it shall be in accordance with the Chinese version. \n\t

For any matter not mentioned in this agreement, you shall comply with the announcements and related rules updated by JGW from time to time. \n\t


JGW “Privacy Policy of JGW Wallet” \n\t

Version1.1 Jun 11, 2018 \n\t

JGW (hereinafter referred to as “JGW” or “We”) respects and protects the privacy of users (hereinafter referred to as “You” or “Users”), when you use JGW Wallet, JGW shall collect and use your personal information according to this privacy policy (hereinafter referred to as “This Policy”). \n\t

JGW recommends you to carefully read and understand all contents of this policy before using this product (hereinafter referred to as “JGW Wallet”), the important information including disclaimers shall be reflected in bold form. The definition of related key words under this policy shall be maintained consistent with that of JGW’s “JGW Wallet User Service Agreement”. \n\t

This policy may be updated online by JGW at any time, once released, the updated policy shall replace the original policy, if you don’t accept the terms after modification, please immediately stop using JGW Wallet, your continuous use of JGW Wallet shall be deemed as your acceptance of the policy after such modification. Once being released on JGW Wallet, the modified policy shall immediately and automatically become valid. \n\t

You know that this policy and other related regulations are applicable to JGW Wallet or the DApp or App that JGW independently owns on JGW Wallet. \n\t

1. Which information we collect from you \n\t

Please know that our collection of your information as follows is for the purpose of meeting your demand for JGW Wallet service, and we attach importance to the protection of your privacy. When collecting your information, we will strictly comply with the principles of “Legality, Just and Necessity”. Besides, you know that if you don’t provide the related information needed for our service, your service experience in JGW Wallet may be affected because of it. \n\t

1.1 You authorize use to collect and store your personal information as follows: \n\t

• Identity recognition information, including but not limited to your name, ID certificate, contact address, telephone number, biological characteristics information. \n\t

• Platform operation information, including but not limited to your IP address, device model, device identifier, operating system version information. \n\t

• Payment information, including but not limited to your payment time, payment amount, payment tool, account and other related information. \n\t

• Personal credit information, including but not limited to any of your credit status, credit score, credit report information. \n\t

• Our collection of data is based on the interaction between you and us as well as the choice you made, including your privacy setting and the products and functions used by you. The data collected by us may include SDKAPIJS code version, browser, internet service provider, IP address, platform, timestamp, application identifier, application program version, application distribution channel, independent device identifier, iOS advertising identifier (IDFA), main identifier of Android advertising, network card (MAC) address, international mobile equipment identifier (IMEI), device model, terminal manufacturer, terminal device operating system version, session initiation and stop time, place of language, time zone and network state (WiFi, etc.), hardware, CPU and battery using status, etc. \n\t

• The other personal information of yours collected based on our need regarding specific products and services shall include but not limited to your opinions and suggestions regarding to us and our products or services, the mobile application software and using scenario and using habits or other information that you used to use or frequently use. \n\t

1.2 Protection of user privacy is a basic policy of this company, without your prior consent, JGW Wallet shall not share or transfer your personal information to any third party, but except for the following circumstances: \n\t

 (1) Have obtained your clear consent or authorization in advance; \n\t

 (2) The personal information collected is disclosed to the public by yourself; \n\t

(3) The collected personal information is collected from legally opened information, such as legal news report, government information disclosure and other public channels; \n\t

 (4) For any sharing with the affiliated parties of JGW Wallet, we shall only share the necessary user information, and it shall be bound by the purpose stated in this privacy clause; \n\t

 (5) Provided according to the applicable laws and regulations of local country, requirements of legal procedures, and requirements by administrative agency or judicial agency; \n\t

 (6) When involving merger or acquisition, if involving any transfer of personal information, JGW Wallet will require the receiver of such personal information to continuously accept binding by this policy; \n\t

 (7) We have reason to believe that you have breached certain one (or ones) clauses under this agreement and caused any damage to JGW Wallet or any third party. \n\t

1.3 Our method of collecting information is as follows: \n\t

 (1) You provide information to us. For example, you fill your name, mobile phone number or bank card number on the “Personal Center” page, or provide email address when feedback issues, or you additionally provide to us when using certain service of ours. \n\t

 (2) The information that we obtains when you use JGW Wallet, including your mobile device information and the record of your operation of JGW Wallet and other related information; \n\t

 (3) The entire or partial transaction records that we copy through block chain system. But the transaction record shall be in accordance with the record by block chain system. \n\t

2. How We Use Your Information \n\t

2.1 We use data to continuously improve our products, including adding new functions or capacities. For example, we use the only fingerprint of your mobile device to determine the corresponding relation between your and your wallet. \n\t

2.2 We will timely send important notices to you, such as software updating, change of service agreement and this policy clause. \n\t

2.3 We provide you with multiple login options in the “System Setting” of JGW Wallet, so you can conveniently and safely manage your digital assets. \n\t

2.4 We process the feedback submitted by you by collecting your open wallet address and the provided mobile device information. \n\t

2.5 We collect your personal information to implement the internal audit, data analysis and research, etc. of JGW, so as to continuously enhance our service level. \n\t

2.6 According to the “JGW Wallet Service Agreement” and other related regulations of JGW, JGW shall use user information to manage and process the using behaviors of users. \n\t

2.7 Provisions of Laws and Regulations and Requirements for Coordination with Regulatory Agencies. \n\t

2.8 We have introduced the purpose of processing personal data in the text above. The legal basis of our processing of personal data includes: for performance of the contract with you (for example, providing the service requested by you, having identification and verification of you, so you can use the website); for compliance with legal requirements (for example, for compliance with applicable accounting rules, performance of the requirements by law enforcement departments for compulsory disclosure); for protecting the rightful interest of ours (for example, managing our relationship with you, for ensuring the safety of our service, and for communication with you about our products and services); and on the basis of consent by our clients (for example, releasing cookies, sharing your information with third party for purpose of advertising and promotion). \n\t

3. How You Control Your Own Information \n\t

You have independent controlling right of your own personal information in JGW Wallet: \n\t

3.1 You can input your other wallets into JGW Wallet in the method of wallet synchronization, or input your wallets in JGW Wallet to other digital assets management wallets. JGW Wallet will show you the information of input wallets. \n\t

3.2 You know that you can modify your digital asset type, transfer, receive payments and other activities through the consents of “Asset” section. \n\t

3.3 You know that you may freely choose to have the following operations in the “My” section of the JGW Wallet: \n\t

 (1) In the “Personal Center”, you don’t need to provide your own name, mobile phone number, bank card number and other related information, but when you use certain service, you need to provide the foresaid information; \n\t

 (2) In “Submit Feedback”, you may propose your questions and improvement suggestions on JGW Wallet to us at any time, we would be very glad to communicate with you and actively improve our service. \n\t

3.4 You know that when we collect information from you for certain purpose, we will notice you in advance, and you will have the right to reject. But at the same time, you also know that when you choose to reject provision of related information, it means that you have given up using the related services of JGW Wallet. \n\t

3.5 You know that you and us have no control over whether your transaction record is opened or not, because of the open-source property of block chain transaction system, your transaction record will be open and transparent in the entire block chain system. \n\t

3.6 You know that after you use the function of JGW Wallet to skip to a third-party DApp, our “JGW Wallet Service Agreement” and “JGW Wallet Privacy Policy” will be no longer applicable, as for the issue of your control over your personal information on third-party DApp, we suggest you to carefully read and understand the privacy rules and related user service agreement and other related contents of third-party DApp before using it. \n\t

3.7 You shall have the right to require us to update, change or delete the related information of yours. \n\t

3.8 You know that we can collect your information as required in Article 1.2 of this Policy without the need to obtain authorization and consent from you. \n\t

3.9 According to applicable laws, you shall have the right to oppose or require limitation of the processing of your personal data, and require the right to access, correction, deletion and bringing of your personal data. \n\t

Under the precondition that the use of your information is based on your consent, you shall have the right to revoke such consent at any time, but the revocation of consent shall not affect the legality of the previous data processing based on consent. \n\t

You may propose your requirement to us through [Feedback of Opinion]. \n\t

If you find out there is any change or inaccuracy of your information, please notice us of such change, so our record can be updated or corrected. If you think that our processing of your personal data has violated any applicable law, you may file complaint to the regulatory authority. \n\t

The time for us to preserve your personal data shall depend on the demand for providing service or product to you, or recognized based on the requirements or permission of applicable laws, such as tax law or accounting law. \n\t

4. We May Share or Transmit Your Information \n\t

4.1 In order to optimize our products and provide you with higher-quality service, we will share personal data with the suppliers or agencies providing service to us for the purpose regulated in this privacy policy. For example, the company we hire to provide data analysis service may need to collect and access personal data for data statistics and analysis. Under such circumstance, these companies must comply with our requirements on data privacy and safety. \n\t

4.2 Without your prior consent, JGW will not share or transfer your personal information to any third party, except for the following circumstances: \n\t

 (1) Have obtained your clear consent or authorization in advance; \n\t

 (2) The personal information collected is disclosed to the public by yourself; \n\t

 (3) The collected personal information is collected from legally opened information, such as legal news report, government information disclosure and other public channels; \n\t

 (4) For any sharing with the affiliated parties of JGW Wallet, we shall only share the necessary user information, and it shall be bound by the purpose stated in this privacy clause; \n\t

 (5) Provided according to the applicable laws and regulations of local country, requirements of legal procedures, and requirements by administrative agency or judicial agency; \n\t

 (6) When involving merger or acquisition, if involving any transfer of personal information, JGW Wallet will require the receiver of such personal information to continuously accept binding by this policy; \n\t

4.3 Our business may require us to transfer your personal data to other countries beyond the European Economic Region, these countries may include China or Singapore. We will adopt proper measures to ensure the recipients of your personal data to perform confidentiality obligations, and ensure the execution of measures such as standard contractual terms. You may obtain such terms by contacting our help center. \n\t

5. How We Protect Your Information \n\t

5.1 If JGW is suspended of operation, JGW will timely stop the activity of continuous collection of your personal information, and will announce the notice of operation suspension in JGW Wallet, and will delete or have anonymization treatment of your personal information within reasonable period. \n\t

5.2 In order to protect your personal information, JGW will adopt technical measures for data safety, enhance internal compliance level, increase information safety trainings on internal employees, and set safety access limitation on related data or other related methods to safely protect your private information. \n\t

5.3 We will update the materials for wallet using and information protection in the “Help Center” section of JGW Wallet for your reference. \n\t

6. Protection of Minors \n\t

We make the following special regulation for protecting minors who haven’t turned 18 years old yet: \n\t

6.1 Minors shall use the related services of JGW under the instruction of their guardians. \n\t

6.2 We suggest the parents and guardians of minors to instruct minors to use JGW Wallet under the precondition of reading this policy, the “JGW Wallet Service Agreement” and our other related rules. \n\t

6.3  JGW Wallet will protect the confidentiality and safety of the personal information of minors according to related national laws and regulations. \n\t

7. Disclaimer \n\t

7.1 Please note that after accessing to third-party DApp through JGW Wallet, you shall be applicable to the privacy policy released by such third-party DApp. The collection and use of your personal information by such third-party DApp are not controlled by JGW, and shall not be bound by this policy. JGW can’t guarantee such third-party DApp to adopt personal information protection measures based on the requirements of JGW. \n\t

7.2 You should prudently choose and use third-party DApp, and properly protect your own personal information, JGW shall not take any liability for the privacy protection by other third-party DApp. \n\t

7.3 JGW will protect your personal information by adopting as much reasonable safety measures as possible under current technical levels and conditions, so as to avoid information disclosure, alteration or destruction. JGW uses wireless method to transmit data, therefore, JGW is unable to ensure the privacy and safety of data transmitted through wireless network. \n\t

8. Applicability of Law and Dispute Settlement \n\t

8.1 The effect, interpretation, change, execution and dispute settlement of this agreement and its modified versions shall all be applicable to the laws of the United Kingdom of Great Britain and Northern Ireland, if there is no related laws, they shall be applicable to international business practices and (or) industrial practices. \n\t

8.2 If there is any dispute or disagreement between you and JGW, it shall be settled firstly through friendly consultation, if such consultation fails, either party may submit it to the local court with jurisdiction where JGW is located. \n\t

9. Others \n\t

9.1 You need to comprehensively understand and comply with all the related laws, regulations and rules related to your use of JGW services in your judicial jurisdiction. \n\t

9.2 In the process of your use of JGW services, for any problem encountered regarding use of personal information, you may contact us by submitting feedback on JGW Wallet. \n\t

9.3 You may check this policy and other service rules of JGW in JGW Wallet. We encourage you to check the service agreement and privacy policy of JGW every time when you access to JGW Wallet. \n\t

9.4 Nt Any translation version of this policy is provided for the convenience of users only, and has no intention of modifying terms of this policy. If there is any conflict between Chinese version of this policy and its non-Chinese version, it shall be in accordance with the Chinese version. \n\t

9.5 This agreement shall be applicable since Jun 25, 2018. \n\t

For any matter not mentioned in this policy, you shall comply with the announcements and related rules updated by JGW from time to time. \n\t
        JGW
    </string>
</resources>
